

CONTACT

- +63-9352108667
- johnrobertllanasas@gmail.com
- Borongan City, Eastern Samar, Philippines 6800

EDUCATION

2015 - 2018 AMA COMPUTER COLLEGE

• Bachelor of Science in Information Technology

2010 - 2014

SAINT MARY'S HIGHSCHOOL

SKILLS

- Link Building
- SEO
- Web Research
- Keyword Research
- Content Strategist
- Email Marketing

LANGUAGES

- English (Fluent)
- Tagalog (Fluent)
- Waray Waray (Intermediate)

JOHN ROBERT G. LLANASAS

SFO LINK BUILDING SPECIALIST

PROFILE

Over the last 4 years, I have helped a wide range of websites and online businesses increase their search engine visibility through SEO strategy. I have worked with different SEO companies in managing their SEO and link outreach campaigns.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Insivia

2021 - 2023

Full-time Link Builder

- · Crafting and implementing effective link building strategies tailored to the needs of technology and SaaS clients to enhance their online presence and search engine rankings.
- Identifying and reaching out to potential link partners, bloggers, and influencers to establish relationships and secure high-quality backlinks.
- Monitoring the effectiveness of link building campaigns using various SEO tools and platforms, and providing detailed reports on progress and results to clients.

Achieve IT

2022 - 2024

Link Builder

• Link building manager for multiple clients, tasks include link research, contact hunting, and managing email outreach.

Freight Processing Outsourcing Solution Inc.

Database Administrator

2018 - 2020

· Managing and supervising the system's data and performing other related duties.

SEMINARS AND TRAININGS ATTENDED:

- · Attended the All White Hat SEO training and passed the qualifying exam
- Link Prospecting & Outreach (The blueprint training)
- Take the Semrush SEO Course and passed the exam

TOOLS I USE:

Ahrefs

MOZ

Hunter

GSC

Semrush

Apollo

Buzzstream
Screaming Frog

REFERENCE

Tony Zavas

Chief Revenue Officer at Insivia

Email: tony@insivia.com

Joshua Walter

CEO at Achieve IT

Email: josh@achieveonline.ca